Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 75, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 75, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Medical Plan: For Ford Salaried Men and Women and Their Families, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 46)
    Notes: March 1975
- Box: 75, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 75, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Systems - Democracy in Action, 1953; Publication (Box 75, Folder 47)
    Author: R.E. Roberts
    Notes: November 12, 1951
- Box: 75, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 75, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Management's Attitude Toward Safety, 1954; Publication (Box 75, Folder 48)
    Author: Robert T. Ross
    Notes: May 16, 1950
- Box: 75, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 75, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: The 1955 Ford-UAW Agreement, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 49)
    Author: John J. DeMott, Jr.
    Notes: March 8, 1956
- Box: 75, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 75, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: You Can't Stand Still, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 50)
    Author: Manton M. Cummins
    Notes: November 9, 1955
- Box: 75, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 75, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Medical Insurance Plan: For Ford Salaried Men and Women and Their Families, 1974; Publication (Box 75, Folder 51)
- Box: 75, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 75, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Savings and Stock Investment Plan: For Salaried Employees, 1974; Publication (Box 75, Folder 52)
- Box: 75, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 75, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Retired Employee Medical Insurance Plan: For Ford Motor Company Retired Salaried Men and Women and Their Families, 1974; Publication (Box 75, Folder 53)
- Box: 75, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 75, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Ford Medical Insurance Plan: For Ford Motor Company Salaried Men and Women and Their Families, 1967; Publication (Box 75, Folder 54)
    Notes: November 1965
- Box: 75, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 75, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Ford Motor Company Organizational Chart, 1967; Publication (Box 75, Folder 55)
    Notes: May 1, 1967
- Box: 75, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 75, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: The Impact of Layoff and Recall at Ford-Windsor, 1967; Publication (Box 75, Folder 56)
    Author: C.M. Birch; J.B. Gertz
- Box: 75, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 75, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Savings and Stock Investment Plan For Salaried Employees, 1971; Publication (Box 75, Folder 57)
- Box: 75, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 75, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Savings and Stock Investment Plan for Salaried Employees, 1967; Publication (Box 75, Folder 58)
    Notes: April 1967
- Box: 75, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 75, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Expanding Your Horizons with Ford Motor Company, 1967; Publication (Box 75, Folder 59)
- Box: 75, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 75, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Retired Employee Medical Insurance Plan, 1967; Publication (Box 75, Folder 60)
- Box: 75, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 75, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Ford Motor Company Salaried Employee Information Bulletin: Savings and Stock Investment Program for Salaried Employees, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 61)
    Notes: December 20, 1955
- Box: 75, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 75, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Staff, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 62)
    Notes: January 23, 1956
- Box: 75, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 75, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: News Letter for Salaried Men and Women of the Ford Motor Company: Ford Seperation Allowance Plan Brings Greater Security to Salaried Employees, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 63)
    Notes: September 1955
- Box: 75, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 75, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Ford Motor Company - UAW Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan: Identification Card, 1960; Publication (Box 75, Folder 64)
  - Item 2: Withdrawal of Appeal for Supplemental Unemployment Benefits, 1960; Publication (Box 75, Folder 64)
  - Item 3: Application for Alternate Unemployment Benefit, 1960; Publication (Box 75, Folder 64)
  - Item 4: Ford Motor Company - UAW Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 75, Folder 64)
  - Item 5: Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan Exemption Statement, 1960; Publication (Box 75, Folder 64)
  - Item 6: Company Notice of Overpayment of Supplemental Unemployment Benefits or Separation Payment, 1960; Publication (Box 75, Folder 64)
  - Item 7: Notice of Company Denial or Suspension of Supplemental Employee Benefits or Separation Payment, 1960; Publication (Box 75, Folder 64)
- Box: 75, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 75, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Patents in the General Electric Company: An Outline for General Electric Inventors, 1955; Publication (Box 75, Folder 65)
  - Item 2: Patents in the General Electric Company: An Outline for General Electric Engineers, 1953; Publication (Box 75, Folder 65)
- Box: 75, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 75, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: How Your Laws are Made in the Congress of the United States, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 66)
    Author: William Jackman
- Box: 75, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 75, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: You and Labor Law, 1950; Publication (Box 75, Folder 67)
    Author: John F. Simons
- Box: 75, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 75, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: General Electric Insurance Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 75, Folder 68)
- Box: 75, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 75, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: General Electric Pension Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 75, Folder 69)
- Box: 75, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 75, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: GE Pensioners Hospitalization Plan and Trust as Amended 1950, 1951; Publication (Box 75, Folder 70)
- Box: 75, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 75, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: The Ford Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 71)
    Author: Joseph A. O'Reilly
- Box: 75, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 75, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: How a Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan Affects Production Planning, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 72)
    Author: Frank C. McCoard
    Notes: November 1, 1955
- Box: 75, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 75, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: The 1955 Ford-UAW Contract, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 73)
- Box: 75, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 75, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: The Ford Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 74)
    Author: Karlton W. Pierce
    Notes: September 8, 1955
- Box: 75, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 75, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: The Ford Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan and its Effect on State Unemployment Compensation Laws, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 75)
    Author: Wilbur C. Hampton
    Notes: September 16, 1955
- Box: 75, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 75, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: The Ford Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 76)
    Notes: November 21, 1955
- Box: 75, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 75, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Thaddeus J. Obal: The Ford Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 77)
    Author: Thaddeus J. Obal
    Notes: November 3, 1955
  - Item 2: Karlton W. Pierce: The Ford Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 77)
    Notes: November 17, 1955
- Box: 75, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 75, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: What Kind of Citizens Are We?, 1954; Publication (Box 75, Folder 78)
    Notes: February 23, 1950
- Box: 75, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 75, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Annual Forum of Agriculture, Labor and Industry, 1954; Publication (Box 75, Folder 79)
    Author: John S. Bugas
- Box: 75, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 75, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Characteristics of the Auto Industry, Publication (Box 75, Folder 80)
- Box: 75, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 75, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: People ARE Important, 1954; Publication (Box 75, Folder 81)
    Notes: January 30, 1954
- Box: 75, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 75, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: The New Labor Agreements in the Automobile Industry, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 82)
    Author: John J. DeMott
- Box: 75, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 75, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: James M. Osborne: The Ford Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 83)
- Box: 75, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 75, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Cooperation for Progress, 1954; Publication (Box 75, Folder 84)
    Author: Benson Ford
- Box: 75, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 75, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Our Jobs are Bigger Than we Think, 1954; Publication (Box 75, Folder 85)
    Author: Del S. Harder
- Box: 75, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 75, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Management's Responsibility for Keeping Employees Informed, 1954; Publication (Box 75, Folder 86)
- Box: 75, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 75, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: Malcolm L. Denise: The Ford Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 87)
- Box: 75, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 75, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: The Ford Spirit, 1954; Publication (Box 75, Folder 88)
    Author: Ernest R. Breech
- Box: 75, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 75, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Let's Quit Talking to Ourselves, 1953; Publication (Box 75, Folder 89)
- Box: 75, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 75, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Guaranteed Annual Wage - Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plans - A Consideration of the Practicial Problems Posed by This New Development in Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 90)
    Notes: September 14, 1955
- Box: 75, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 75, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: The Ford Story, 1954; Publication (Box 75, Folder 91)
    Notes: November 24, 1953
- Box: 75, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 75, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: The Ford Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan and How it Works, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 92)
    Notes: September 30, 1955
- Box: 75, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 75, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Current Planning at Ford Motor Company, 1954; Publication (Box 75, Folder 93)
    Author: Robert J. Hampson
    Notes: February 21, 1950
- Box: 75, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 75, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Employee Morale in a Mass Production Industry, 1954; Publication (Box 75, Folder 94)
    Author: Robert S. Dunham
    Notes: June 19, 1950
- Box: 75, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 75, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: President's Committee on Employment of the Pysically Handicapped, 1954; Publication (Box 75, Folder 95)
    Notes: September 22, 1953
- Box: 75, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 75, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Safety in Steel, 1954; Publication (Box 75, Folder 96)
    Author: Otis U. Walker
- Box: 75, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 75, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: Thirty-Year Review of the General Electric Company, 1930; Publication (Box 75, Folder 97)
- Box: 75, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 75, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: The GE News Objectives and How to Achieve Them: Employee Communication Part 2: The GE News, 1955; Publication (Box 75, Folder 98)
- Box: 75, Folder: 99, Publication (Box 75, Folder 99)
  - Item 1: A General Electric Scrapbook History with Commentary, Publication (Box 75, Folder 99)
- Box: 75, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 75, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: Employee and Plant Community Relations Publications, 1953; Publication (Box 75, Folder 100)
- Box: 75, Folder: 101, Publication (Box 75, Folder 101)
  - Item 1: Good Business Citizenship: The Big Challenge in Community Relations, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 101)
- Box: 75, Folder: 102, Publication (Box 75, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: The Use of Newspaper Advertising in Plant Community Relations: A Review of Successful Campaigns, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 102)
- Box: 75, Folder: 103, Publication (Box 75, Folder 103)
  - Item 1: Beyond Our Walls: A Program for Interpreting G.E. to the Community, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 103)
- Box: 75, Folder: 104, Publication (Box 75, Folder 104)
  - Item 1: The General Electric Lockland Plan: A Case History of a Planned Community Advertising Program, 1953; Publication (Box 75, Folder 104)
- Box: 75, Folder: 105, Publication (Box 75, Folder 105)
  - Item 1: How to Turn Dropouts into Steady Workers, 1970; Publication (Box 75, Folder 105)
    Notes: August 31, 1968
  - Item 2: Industrial Relations Reference Manual, 1958; Publication (Box 75, Folder 105)
    Notes: January 30, 1958
- Box: 76, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Program for Clergy: Employee and Plan Community Relations, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Box: 76, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: With the Help of our Churches, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Box: 76, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Erie Story: A Case History of a Successful Community Television Series, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Box: 76, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Plant Dedications, Plant Tours, and Open House: A Review of Company Plans and Practices, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Box: 76, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The General Electric Lockland Plan: A Case History of a Planned Community Advertising Program, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Box: 76, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Employees Community Service Funds: A Review of Company Plans and Practices, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Box: 76, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A Community Relations Program for Physicians, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Box: 76, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Welcome, Doctor, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Box: 76, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Highlights of the General Electric Economic Education Program, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Box: 76, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A Checklist of Plant Community Relations Activities, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Box: 76, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: A Yardstick to Better Government for You, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Box: 76, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Employee Relations News Letter: The Community's Problem in Getting and Keeping Good Employers, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 12)
    Notes: June 3, 1955
- Box: 76, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The General Electric Louisville Plan: A Case History of General Electric's Entry into Louisville, Kentucky, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 13)
- Box: 76, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Junior Achievement: An Effective Training Program for Teaching Youth About the American Business System, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 14)
- Box: 76, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Mailings to Civic Thought Leaders: An Essential Part of the Plant Community Relations Program, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 15)
- Box: 76, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Plant Community Relations, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 16)
- Box: 76, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Why There is a Strike at General Electric, 1960; Publication (Box 76, Folder 17)
    Author: Al Hartnett; James B. Carey
- Box: 76, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: 1962 Annual Report, 1963; Publication (Box 76, Folder 18)
- Box: 76, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Automation in General Electric: The Human Side of the Story, 1963; Publication (Box 76, Folder 19)
- Box: 76, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The General Electric Plant Community Relations Program, 1953; Publication (Box 76, Folder 20)
    Author: R.T. Borth
- Box: 76, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Communications in a Work Stoppage: A Case History, 1957; Publication (Box 76, Folder 21)
    Author: A.C. Stevens
- Box: 76, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: United States of America Before the National Labor Relations Board Second Region in the Matter of General Electric Company and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Respondent's Brief for Trial Examiner Part I, 1966; Publication (Box 76, Folder 22)
    Author: David L. Benetar; Thomas F. Hilbert, Jr.; Robert C. Isaacs; Sanford Browde
- Box: 76, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: United States of America Before the National Labor Relations Board Second Region in the Matter of General Electric Company and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO: Respondent's Brief for Trial Examiner Part 2, 1966; Publication (Box 76, Folder 23)
- Box: 76, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: United States of America Before the National Labor Relations Board Second Region in the Matter of General Electric Company and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO: Respondent's Reply Brief for Trial Examiner, 1966; Publication (Box 76, Folder 24)
- Box: 76, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Management Research and Development Institute: Materials Used in the Advanced Management Course, 1960; Publication (Box 76, Folder 25)
    Author: Paul Kurzman
- Box: 76, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Supervisory Problems, 1960; Publication (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Suggestion Plan: Electrochemicals Department, 1946; Publication (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: General Safety Standards, 1954; Publication (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Revised Catalog of Available Materials for Teaching and Using Creative Problem-Solving, Publication (Box 76, Folder 26)
- Box: 76, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: A Program for Interpreting General Electric to the Farm Neighbors, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 27)
- Box: 76, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Supervisory Problems, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 28)
- Box: 76, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: The Organization and Tasks of the Engineering Department: A Brief Description of Firestone Tire & Rubber Company Guided Missile Division, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 29)
- Box: 76, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Career Opportunities, 1961; Publication (Box 76, Folder 30)
    Author: C.H. Bell
- Box: 76, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Today: Organization, Financial Data, A Look at the Future, 1957; Publication (Box 76, Folder 31)
- Box: 76, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Master Agreement Between General Mills, Inc. and American Federation of Grain Millers (AFL), 1950; Publication (Box 76, Folder 32)
    Notes: Effective March 1, 1950, to April 1, 1952
- Box: 76, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Employees' Suggestion System, 1950; Publication (Box 76, Folder 33)
- Box: 76, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 76, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Subject Register Classification Code, 1950; Publication (Box 76, Folder 34)
- Box: 76, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 76, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Employee's Suggestion Form, 1950; Publication (Box 76, Folder 35)
- Box: 76, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 76, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Basic Policies on Which Our Company Operates, 1950; Publication (Box 76, Folder 36)
- Box: 76, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 76, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Front Page: From the Department of Public Services, 1950; Publication (Box 76, Folder 37)
    Author: L.N. Perrin
- Box: 76, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 76, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Spotlight on OSHA, 1973; Publication (Box 76, Folder 38)
    Author: R.D. Vandenberg
- Box: 76, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 76, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Spotlight on Safety, 1973; Publication (Box 76, Folder 39)
- Box: 76, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 76, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: "You and the Master Agreement": Administrative Guide for Programmed Introduction Course, 1971; Publication (Box 76, Folder 40)
- Box: 76, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 76, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: "You and the Master Agreement": Introduction, 1968; Publication (Box 76, Folder 41)
- Box: 76, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 76, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: "You and the Master Agreement": Training Outline, 1971; Publication (Box 76, Folder 42)
- Box: 76, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 76, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: "You and the Master Agreement": Training Outline (For Humac Unit), 1971; Publication (Box 76, Folder 43)
- Box: 76, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 76, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Administrative Guide for the General Mills Related Traning Course "Our Company", 1955; Publication (Box 76, Folder 44)
- Box: 76, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 76, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Administrative Guide: General Mills the Flour Business Classroom Course, 1950; Publication (Box 76, Folder 45)
- Box: 76, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 76, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Management Practices for Plant Supervisors, 1957; Publication (Box 76, Folder 46)
- Box: 76, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 76, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Working at Kool-Aid: Work and Pay Policies for Hourly Employees, 1970; Publication (Box 76, Folder 47)
  - Item 2: General Foods Corporation Vacation Plan for Salaried Employees, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 47)
  - Item 3: General Foods Corporation Benefits Program for Salaried Employees: Highlights, 1970; Publication (Box 76, Folder 47)
- Box: 76, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 76, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Industrial Truck Operating Instructions, 1966; Publication (Box 76, Folder 48)
  - Item 2: Intra-Company Correspondence: Company Car Safety Program, 1965; Publication (Box 76, Folder 48)
    Author: E.W. Rawlings
  - Item 3: Plant Management Responsibilities in the Basic Accident Prevention Program, 1966; Publication (Box 76, Folder 48)
- Box: 76, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 76, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: "You and the Master Agreement" Programmed Instruction Course: Training Outline, 1968; Publication (Box 76, Folder 49)
  - Item 2: "You and the Master Agreement": Introduction, 1968; Publication (Box 76, Folder 49)
  - Item 3: Supervisors' Labor Relations Training Program Supplemental Agreement: Administrative Guide, 1964; Publication (Box 76, Folder 49)
  - Item 4: Management Practices for Plant Supervisors, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 49)
  - Item 5: Congratulations Flour Business and Basic Milling Course Graduates, 1952; Publication (Box 76, Folder 49)
  - Item 6: Maintenance Selection and Training Program Addendum: Package Foods Plant, Publication (Box 76, Folder 49)
  - Item 7: "You and the Master Agreement": Conference Course Outline, 1968; Publication (Box 76, Folder 49)
  - Item 8: Supervisors' Labor Relations Training Program Supplemental Agreement: Introduction, 1965; Publication (Box 76, Folder 49)
  - Item 9: Supervisors' Labor Relations Training Program Supplemental Agreement: Course Outline, 1965; Publication (Box 76, Folder 49)
- Box: 76, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 76, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Maintenance Training Program, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 50)
- Box: 76, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 76, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: What About This Salary Administration Program?, Publication (Box 76, Folder 51)
- Box: 77, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Employee Entrance, 1962; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Termination Notice, 1962; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Personal Data Change, 1962; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Employee Status Change, 1962; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Box: 77, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Operating Chart: Division of the Gillette Company, 1962; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Box: 77, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Employee Entrance, 1968; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Employee Status Change, 1968; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Termination Notice, 1968; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)